Guide to the Brooklyn letterhead collection BCMS.0008
Brooklyn Collection
- Blumenstein, E.G., 1892
  Carpenters. 797 Monroe Street [formerly 93 5th Street]
- Bnois Chesed Shel Emes Daughters of the True Benevolence, 1921
- Board of American Hazan-Ministers
  111 East 21st Street
- Board of Education Bureau of Construction and Maintenance, 1926
  re: PS 45. Flatbush Avenue Ext. and Concord Street
- Bodkin & Schinnagel, 1868
  Plumbers, gas and steam fitters. 743 Myrtle Avenue bet. Spencer and Walworth Sts.
- Boecher, L. & Co., 1890
  Builders' hardware. 30 Throop Ave cor. Gwinnett St.
- Boehne, H.F., 1874
  Merchant tailor. 198 DeKalb Avenue
- Boehner,William J. & Co., 1918, 1919, 1920
  Hatters' fur manufacturers and ginseng dealers. Franklin Ave. and Wallabout St.
- Bogert, J.B., 1894
  Carpenter and builder. Clifton Place, near Classon Avenue
- Bohack, H.C. Co., 1935
  Grocery stores. Bohack Square, 49-03 Metropolitan Avenue
- Bohn, A.W. & W., 1906
  Coffees, spices, teas. 50 Washington Ave.
- Bohnson, Charles F., 1883, 1891
  Hay, straw, grain and feed dealer. 282 Division Ave. cor. Harrison Avenue; Junc. Flushing Ave., Tompkins Ave. & Delmonico Place
- Boise & Nash Realty Co., Inc., 1939
  Real estate and insurance. 1515 Flatbush Avenue corner Glenwood Road
- Bolstein, J., Mrs., 1890
  Glass dealer. 692 DeKalb Avenue
- Bolstein, M., 1888
  Glass dealer.
- Bolton Drug Co., The, 1898
  Wholesale druggists. 264, 266, 268, 270 Fulton Street
- Bond and Mortgage Guarantee Company, 1910, 1919, 1930
  Bonds and mortgages. 175 Remsen Street
- Booth, Chas., 1883, 1888, 1889
  Tin, copper, and sheet iron worker. 269 Court Street, bet. Butler & Douglass Sts.
- Boro Electric Beer Pipe Cleaners, 1937
  Beer pipe cleaner, repairer, and installer.
- Bors, Martin, 1897
  Hardware. 1866 Fulton Street
- Borsum Bros., 1888
  Metal and glass polish. 91 Cliff Street, near Brooklyn Bridge
- Bosch, John, 1880, 1889, 1894
  Plumber, gas and steam fitter. 708 Flushing Ave., near Throop Ave.; 696 Flushing Ave. & 76 Central Ave.
- Bossert, Hotel
  Montague, Hicks, and Remsen Streets
- Boston Steam Carpet Beating Co., The, 1872
  Carpet cleaners. cor. Bond and Third Streets
- Boulton, Jessie, 1890
  Carpenter. 250 West Baltic Street, near Court
- Boulton, P., 1895
  Carpenter and builder. 250 Baltic Street
- Bowers, 1885
  Photographer. 340 Fulton cor. Court St.
- Bowne, S.W. (& Co.), 1879, 1887, 1894, 1895, 1896, 1900, 1911
  Hay, straw, grain, flour and feed dealer. Gowanus Canal, near Hamilton Avenue, and Third Avenue, cor. 20th Street; Elevator and mills, 593 to 625 Smith Street
- Boyce, Charles A., 1885
  Painter and paper hanger. 29 McDougal St. near Ralph Ave.
- Boyce, M.A., 1891
  Dealer in paints, oils, glass, and putty; wall paper, window shades etc.. 30 McDougal St. near Ralph Ave.
- Boyd, E.S., 1890
  Carpenter and builder. Successor to Hartt & Boyd. 300 and 302 Navy Street
- Boyd's City Dispatch, 1927
  Advertising. 114 to 120 East 23rd Street
- Boyle, Henry, 1860, 1869
  Furniture and bedding. 124, 125 Atlantic Street, third door from Henry
- Boyle, James, 1861, 1864
  Plumber, gas and steam fitter. 6 Fulton Avenue, bet. Pearl and Jay Streets
- Boyle, P., 1883
  Horseshoer. 19 Hoyt Street near Fulton Street
- Boyne & Toohill, 1868, 1869
  Plumbers, steam and gas fitters. 34 Hamilton Avenue
- Boys' Welcome Hall
  Boys' Club. 185 Chauncey Street
- Brackett, George C., 1868, 1869
  Teacher.
- Bradford, F.W., 1901
  Roofing, furnaces and ranges. Bay 19th St. near Bath Ave.
- Bradley, Daniel, 1861, 1872
  Stoves, ranges, furnaces, tin and iron ware. 136 York Street, near Charles; Tin, copper, and sheet iron worker. 184 York Street, near Charles
- Bradley, John B., 1883, 1885
  Iron works. 93 Wyckoff Street, near Smith
- Bradley, William (& Sons), 1879, 1884
  Stone dealer. Yard, Nevins Street, cor. Butler
- Brady, Wesley S., 1899
  Carpenter and builder; contractor. 335 Flatbush Avenue, opp. Seventh
- Braeunlich, Lilly, Miss, 1878
  Piano teacher
- Braiding & Packing Works of America Inc., 1927
  Manufacturers of steam and water packings. 250-252 46th Street
- Brainerd, S.W., 1868, 1869
  Stone worker. Corner of Second and South First Sts.
- Bramm, John, 1878, 1882
  Manufacturers of tabacoo and fine segars. 32 Atlantic Street
- Branagan, B., 1897
  Metal roofer, tin and sheet iron worker. 448 Gates Avenue
- Branagan, Joseph A., 1937
  Jeweler. 35 Tennis Court
- Brandeis & Wickert, 1870
  Lead pipe, bronze colors, and dealers in plumbers' materials. 48 Fulton Street
- Brandis, F.E. Sons & Co., 1898, 1899, 1910
  Manufacturers of civil engineers', surveyors', and astronomical instruments. 764-768 Lexington Ave.; 812-814 Gates Avenue
- Brandt, George W. / Brandt & Co., 1884, 1887, 1893
  Carpenter and builder; Lumber dealer; Lumber, sash, blinds and doors. 3rd Ave. and 66th St.; 1st Ave and 66th St.
- Brass Goods Manufacturing Company, 1899, 1902
  Brass and tin goods. 86 to 92 Third Street
- Brazill, William P., 1889
  Mason and builder. 335 Graham Avenue
- Brechtlein, M., 1901
  Builders' hardware. 620-622 DeKalb Ave.
- Brehm Brothers, 1876
  Steam segar box manufacturers. 18 Throop Avenue, near Broadway
- Brennan, John J., 1882, 1887
  Carpenter and builder. 189 Lee Ave., bet. Rutledge and Heyward Sts.; 108 Heyward Street, near Lee Avenue
- Brennan & White, 1895
  Shoe manufacturer. 54-74 Classon Avenue
- Brenneis & Hanold, 1899
  Carpenters and builders. 280 Boerum Street, bet. Bushwick Ave. & White St.
- Brien, Adams & Brien / Martin J. Brien, 1864, 1873, 1874, 1877, 1878
  Plumbers and gas fitters. 165, 166 Atlantic Street
- Brien, James G., 1870
  Painter and dealer in painters' goods. 180 Jay Street
- Brillo Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1931
  Manufacturer of Brillo household cleanser. 205-213 Water Street
- Brislin, John A. Fuel Corporation, 1933
  Coal dealers. Avenue U & Mill Avenue, Mill Basin
- Bristol-Myers Company, 1918
  Chemists. 281 Greene Avenue
- Broadway Merchants' Association, 1930
  10 Howard Avenue (secretary)
- Broncho Company, The, 1913
  Manufacturers of medicine [?]. 129 St. James Place
- Bronson Brothers, 1881
  Builders' hardware and house-furnishing goods. 338 Myrtle Avenue, cor. Carlton Avenue, 823 Myrtle Avenue, near Marcy Avenue
- Brooklyn [magazine], 1924
  32 Court Street
- Brooklyn Advance Job Printing Department, The, 1893
  Printers. 2921 Atlantic Ave., near Warwick St.
- Brooklyn Alcatraz Asphalt Company, The, 1898, 1909
  Asphalt dealer. Third Street, near Third Avenue; 407 Hamilton Avenue
- Brooklyn Ash Removal Company, Inc., 1932
  Ash removal. 25 Court Street
- Brooklyn Beef Co., 1891, 1898
  Butcher. 74 & 76 Atlantic Avenue
- Brooklyn Benevolent Society, The, 1863, 1865
  Benevolent society. 66 Amity St.
- Brooklyn Blue Print Works, 1919
  Printers. 7 Myrtle Avenue
- Brooklyn Borough President, 1924, 1930, 1932, 1939-1941, 1948, 2002
  Edward Riegelmann, Henry Hesterberg, Raymond V. Ingersoll, John Cashmore, Marty Markowitz.
- Brooklyn Borough President Topographical Bureau, 1916, 1918
  Charles R. Ward, Chief Engineer.
- Brooklyn Brass Mfg Co, 1899
  Brass manufacturing. 46 West Broadway, New York NY
- Brooklyn Bridge [magazine]
  388 Atlantic Avenue
- Brooklyn Bureau of Buildings, 1929
- Brooklyn Bureau of Charities Wood Yard
  80 Pacific Street
- Brooklyn C.Y.O., 1965, 1966
  Catholic youth organization. 191 Joralemon Street
- Brooklyn Chair Company, 1889, 1891, 1893, 1897
  118-126 Waverly Ave., near Myrtle Ave.
- Brooklyn Chamber Of Commerce, 1929, 1931
  66 Court Street
- Brooklyn Citizen, The, 1893, 1898, 1899, 1901, 1926
  Newspaper. 397, 399, 401 and 403 Fulton St., opp. City Hall; Willoughby, Adams, and Fulton Sts.
- Brooklyn City News, 1863
  Steam printing. 368 Fulton Street
- Brooklyn City Railroad Company, The, 1921, 1925
  168 Montague Street
- Brooklyn City Safe Deposit Co., The, 1890, 1903, 1912
  Vaults. 177-179 Montague Street, cor. Clinton
- Brooklyn Club, The, 1918
  Social club. 136 Pierrepont Street
- Brooklyn Collectibles (Brian Merlis, Proprieter)
  Antique dealer. 68, 69 Westminster Road, Lynbrook, NY
- Brooklyn Collectors Office, 1867
- Brooklyn College, 1914, 1916, 1946, 1947
  Nostrand Avenue, Carroll and Crown Streets
- Brooklyn Cooperage Company, 1921
  142 Kent Avenue
- Brooklyn Daily Eagle, 1866, 1868, 1880, 1881, 1889, 1890, 1895, 1897, 1898, 1899, 1909, 1913, 1921, 1922, 1926, 1936, 1940
  Newspaper. 1 Van Anden; 34, 36, & 38 Fulton Street; Eagle building, Washington and Johnson Streets; Johnson and Adams Streets
- Brooklyn Daily Times, 1868, 1880, 1890, 1913
  Newspaper. 12 & 14, 24 and 26 Broadway
- Brooklyn Daily Union, The, 1865
  Newspaper. 10 Front Street
- Brooklyn Distilling Company, 1896
  South 9th St. and Kent Ave.
- Brooklyn E.D. Dispensary and Hospital, The, 1900
  Hospital. 106 to 112 South Third Street
- Brooklyn Edison Company, Inc., 1926
  Electricity. 380 Pearl Street
- Brooklyn Electric Lamp and Novelty Co., 1900
  Lamp maker. 278 Fulton Street
- Brooklyn Elevator & Milling Co., 1911
  Miller. 86 & 88 Kent Ave.
- Brooklyn Ferry Co., of New York, 1900
  Ferry. 392 Kent Avenue
- Brooklyn Figure Skating Club, Inc.
  Sports club. 1163 Atlantic Avenue
- Brooklyn Fire Insurance Company, Office of the, 1860
  11 Court, cor. Remsen Street
- Brooklyn Fluorescent Light Co.
  Lighting distributor. 562 Atlantic Avenue
- Brooklyn Gas Light Company, 1856
  Gas distributor. 7 Court Street
- Brooklyn Hardware & Sporting Goods Co., 1890, 1896, 1898, 1899
  601 Fulton Street; 6 Boerum Place
- Brooklyn Hebrew Home & Hospital for the Aged, 1959
  Howard and Dumont Avenues
- Brooklyn Heights Railroad Co., The, 1916
  85 Clinton Street
- Brooklyn Hill Association, The, 1941
  Community association. 343 Carlton Avenue
- Brooklyn Housing Slum Clearing Association, Inc., 1937
  191 Joralemon Street
- Brooklyn Ice Palace
  1163 Atlantic Avenue
- Brooklyn Industrial School Association and Home for Destitute Children, 1885
  Orphanage
- Brooklyn Jewish Ministers Association, 1938
  Religious association. Avenue R at East 16th Street
- Brooklyn Juvenile High School, The, 1866
- Brooklyn Leather Belting Co., 1893, 1897
  355 Kent Avenue
- Brooklyn Lumber Company, 1890, 1895, 1898, 1900, 1901
  Lumber dealer. Hamilton Ave., foot of 15th Street
- Brooklyn-Manhattan Transit Corp, 1925
  Transit company. 85 Clinton Street
- Brooklyn Master Bakers' Association, The, 1918
  Prospect Hall, Prospect Ave., near 5th Avenue
- Brooklyn Metal Decorating Plant, 1903
  Sheet metal decorators. 351-353 Jay St.
- Brooklyn Methodist Episcopal Church Home, The, 1887
- Brooklyn Mill and Lumber Co., The, 1886
  Lumber dealer. cor. Atlantic and Schenectady Avenues
- Brooklyn Mortgage Guaranty and Title Company, 1936
  Mortgage company. Fifth Avenue at 74th Street
- Brooklyn Museum, 1923
- Brooklyn News Company, Inc., 1964-1965
  1 Avenue M
- Brooklyn Orphan Asylum, 1875
- Brooklyn Press Club, 1913-1915
  Professional association. 365 Fulton Street
- Brooklyn Queens & Long Island Section, New York Evening Journal, 1929
  Newspaper. 26 Court Street
- Brooklyn Radio, 1928
  577 Myrtle Avenue
- Brooklyn Real Estate Board, 1936
  100 Livingston Street
- B.R.E. (Brooklyn Real Estate) Review Co., The, 1885
  Publication. 218 Fulton Street
- Brooklyn Savings Bank, The
  Clinton and Pierrepont Sts.
- Brooklyn Shekel and Election Board, 1946
  186 Joralemon Street
- Brooklyn Shield Co., 1883
  Manufacturer of ladies' dress shields. 67 Sumner Avenue
- Brooklyn Standard Union, 1927
  Newspaper. 296 Washington Street
- Brooklyn State Hospital, 1930
  Hospital. 681 Clarkson Avenue
- Brooklyn Sugar Refining Co., 1880
  Sugar refinery. 98 Wall Street
- Brooklyn Symphony Orchestra, 1932
  Symphony orchestra. 1402 8th Avenue (14th Regiment Armory)
- Brooklyn Training School for Nurses, 1894
  Nursing school. Corner DeKalb Ave. and Raymond St.
- Brooklyn Trust Company, 1880, 1894, 1938, 1940
  Bank. 215 Montague, cor. Clinton St.
- Brooklyn Tube Works, 1884
  Steam, water, and gas tubes. 1, 3, 5, 7, 9, 11, 13 Adams Street; Cor. John and Adams Streets
- Brooklyn Union Coal Company, Inc., 1933
  Coal distributor. 185 Montague Street
- Brooklyn Union Gas Company, The, 1898, 1899, 1938, 1950
  Gas distributor. 180 Remsen Street; 366 Fifth Avenue; 19 Duryea Place; 176 Remsen Street
- Brooklyn Union Publishing Co., 1885, 1899
  Corner of Fulton and Front Streets
- Brooklyn Union, The, 1869
  Newspaper. Corner Fulton and Front Streets
- Brooklyn Varnish Mnfg Co., 1896
  35 & 37 Nostrand Ave.
- Brooklyn Warehouse and Storage Company, The, 1903
  335-355 Schermerhorn Street
- Brooklyn Watch Case Co., 1894-1895
  11 John Street
- Brooklyn Week For The Blind, 1960
  Fundraiser. 401 State Street
- Brooklyner Freie Presse, 1892, 1898
  Newspaper. 35 Myrtle Avenue
- Brower, J.C., 1863
  Hardware and house furnishing goods. cor. of Myrtle Avenue and Cumberland Street
- Brown & Davidson, 1894
  Ladder manufacturers and riggers. 185 3rd Ave.
- Brown & McLean, 1875
  Dealers in paper hangings, paints, oil, glass, etc.. 285 Grand Street, near 8th St.
- Brown Bros.
  Meat, poultry, and vegetable market. 209 Grand Street
- Brown, A., 1880
  Mason and builder. 46 Fleet Street
- Brown, A.G., 1890-1891
  Shoe maker. 420 & 422 Bedford Ave. cor. So. 8th St.
- Brown, D.N., 1876
  Carpenter and builder. 696 Bedford Ave., cor. Of Putnam
- Brown, Daniel, 1881
  Mason and plasterer. Cor. Portland Ave. and Fulton Street
- Brown, Edward, 1898
  Livery and boarding stables. Cor. Warren and Henry Streets
- Brown, George J., 1897
  Ship and machine smith. 75 & 77 West Street, corner Milton Street, near 10th and 23rd Street Ferries
- Brown, Henry J., 1874, 1904
  Carpenter and builder, building contractor. 46 & 48 Putnam Ave., cor. Irving Place; 1530, 1532, 1534 Fulton Street
- Brown, J.B., 1869
  Dentist. 299 Jay Street near Fulton Avenue
- Brown, J. Romaine & Co., 1899
  Real estate. 59 West 33rd St.
- Brown, James H., 1885-1886
  Tool manufacturer and sharpener. 139 Third Ave bet. Warren and Baltic Streets
- Brown, Jas., 1892
  Hay, straw, and feed dealer. Pier 2, Wallabout
- Brown, M.S. & P.C., 1880, 1883, 1898
  Locksmiths, bell-hangers, and silver platers; electrical contractors. 5 Myrtle Avenue, near City Hall
- Brown, O.E., 1872
  Gents' furnishing goods and manufacturer of shirts. 232 Fulton Street
- Brown, W.S., 1892
  Real estate. 16 Court Street, Phenix Building
- Browning, King & Co., 1915, 1929
  Clothiers, furnishers and hatters.Fulton Street & Dekalb Avenue
- Bruce, Robert, 1885
  Printer. Fulton and High Street
- Bruen, Francis, 1880, 1886
  Plumber, steam and gas fitter. 515 1/2 Fifth Avenue, near 13th Street; 554 Fifth Avenue, near 15th Street
- Brunswick-Balke-Collender Co., 1918
  Billiard tables and bowling alleys. 29 to 35 West 32nd St, New York NY
- Brush, James L., 1868
  Mason and builder. Corner of Cranberry and Henry Streets
- Brush, S. & Co, 1892
  Fruits and produce. 25 Washington Avenue
- Brust Brothers, 1900
  Gold, silver and nickel platers. 14 and 16 Lorimer Street
- Brustein-Donnell Fuel Oil Corp., 1940
  Fuel oil distributors. 2507 Surf Avenue
- Bryan, Joseph, 1864
  Undertaker. 117 Fourth Street
- Bryan, Joseph, 1868, 1870
  (Men's and boy's) clothing and general furnishing goods. 214 Fulton St., between Pineapple & Clark
- Bryant, C.R., 1879, 1883
  Tin and sheet iron worker. 67 Flatbush Avenue, opp. Third Ave.
- Bryant, Statton & Clark's Business College, 1869
  W.H. Clark, successor. 13, 14, 15, 16, Court Street
- Buchanan, A.'s Sons, 1896
  Hardware. 1587 Fulton Street
- Buck, Thaddeus, 1877, 1881, 1893
  Plumber, steam and gas fitter; lead burner; chemical plumber. 707 Myrtle Avenue, bet. Spencer and Walworth Streets
- Buckley, A.C., 1881, 1886, 1892
  Carpenter and builder. 11 Nevins Street, near Fulton; 200 Prince Street
- Buckley, Edward, 1872
  Pharmacist. 619 Third Avenue
- Buckley, Mrs., 1877
  Dress and cloak making, lingerie, and patterns. 445 Flatbush Avenue, 5th house above Carlton
- Buckley, O.K. Jr., 1866, 1869
- Buckley, William C., 1907
  Goodyear welting. 132, 134, 136 Havemeyer Street
- Budowsky, J., 1919
  Wholesale fish and canned goods dealer. 2310 Mermaid Ave.
- Buell & Co., 1871
  Roofing. 26 Court Street
- Buell, C.S., 1892
  Roofing. 219 Montague Street, cor. Court
- Bullwinkel, J.F., 1880
  Attorney. 177 & 179 Montague Street
- Bulwinkle, John M., 1889, 1898
  Stationer. 413 Fulton Street
- Bunce & Behr, 1870
  Carving, sawing and turning. Junction of Classon and Kent Avenues
- Bunce, John, 1869
  Housekeeping and toys. Cor. of Fulton and Henry Sts.
- Bunce, John, 1872, 1880
  Hardware. 106 Fulton Street
- Bureau of Highways, 1909
  Civic. Room 15, Municipal Building
- Burger & Myer, 1872
  Soap makers. 46 to 56 Kent Avenue, near Division Ave.
- Burger & Hower Brewing Company, 1888
  Brewery. Cor. Leonard & Meserole Sts.
- Burgess, Miss E., 1884
  Florist. 76 Broadway, bet. 2nd & 3rd Sts.s
- Burke, Edmund G. Inc., 1926
  Real estate. 146 Pierrepont Street
- Burke, M., 1873
  Tin and metal roofer. Baltic St., bet. 4th & 5th Avenues
- Burke, R.W. Propeller and Owners, 1881
  Towage. 179 Green St., Greenpoint
- Burke, William, 1883
  Carriage maker. 198 Skillman St., near Willoughby Ave.
- Burkhard, Thos., 1893
  Coppersmith. 494 & 496 Flushing Ave.
- Burl & Kenney Store, 1962
  Equipment corp.. 608-610 Atlantic Ave.
- Burlett, A., 1881
  Paper hanging, decorating, kalcomining etc.
- Burling, Benj., 1881
  Harness and collar maker. 205 Flatbush Ave., near Dean Street
- Burn, George, 1878, 1882, 1887
  Paper-hanging, frescoing and painting. 540 Fulton St., near Flatbush Ave.
- Burnes, E.W., 1874
  Tin and sheet iron worker. 523 Myrtle Avenue
- Burnett, E.H., 1869
  Carpenter and builder. 66 Poplar Street
- Burnett, Garwood, 1877, 1880
  House furnishings. 261 Franklin Ave., south of DeKalb
- Burnett, S.O., 1878, 1879, 1888, 1894, 1898
  Hardware and house furnishing goods. 288 Fulton Street
- Burns Bros. Coal, 1911, 1917, 1924, 1930
  Coal distributer. Foot Adams, 26th, 52nd Sts. and 50 Elmwood Ave.; Glenmore Ave. and Junius Street
- Burns, E. Reed, 1894
  Rouge, composition and buff wheels. 40 & 42 Withers Street
- Burr, Coombs, & Wilson, 1904
  Attorneys. 84 Broadway
- Burrell Brothers, 1899-1900
  Butcher. 18 Clinton St., near Fulton
- Burrill, Henry B., 1867
  Undertaker. 1 Fulton Avenue, corner of Red Hook Lane
- Burrill's, 1889
  Real estate and insurance. 453 Fifth Avenue, near 9th Street
- Burroughs, H.F. & W. & Co., 1878, 1882, 1888
  Masons' materials. Yards, foot of Taylor Street by the Wallabout Bridge and Kent Ave. foot of Hooper St.; Office, foot of Taylor Street
- Burroughs, I. & W., 1876
  Laces and millinery goods. 402 Fulton Street
- Burroughs, Mary A., 1893
  Livery stables. 12-18 Brooklyn Avenue
- Burrows, Stephen J., 1883
  Mason and builder. Leonard and Maujer Streets, 69 Broadway
- Bursc, F.J.W. Co., 1902
  Salt dealer. 427-431 Hamilton Ave., 549-559 Smith St.
- Burt, E.D./Edwin C. & Co., 1874, 1878, 1889
  Shoe store. 287 Fulton St.
- Burtis, Divine Jr., 1899
  Dock, ship yard and saw mill. Foot Conover Street, Red Hook Point
- Burtis & Downing, 1875
  Dock and ship yard. Foot Conover Street, Red Hook Point
- Burtis, Samuel E., 1880
  Hardware and house furnishing goods. Successor to John A. Smith. 135 Myrtle Avenue, cor. Duffield St.
- Bush Company, Limited, The, 1896
  Coal and wood dealers. Foot of 42nd Street
- Bushey, Ira S., 1908
  Shipwright. Foot of 20th Street
- Bushwick Chemical Works, 1891
- Bushwick Community Council, 1936
  894 Bushwick Avenue
- Bushwick Glass Works, 1902
  Glass Makers. Grand and Maujer Streets & Morgan Ave.
- Butler, James J., 1937, 1941
  Real estate and insurance. 2131 Flatbush Avenue
- Butler, John, 1863
  Plumber and gas fitter. 112 Fulton & 15 Henry Streets
- Byers, Samuel A., 1880-1881
  Shoe store. 527 Fulton Street, near Duffield
- Cafiero, Joseph Lumber Co., Inc., 1943
  Lumber distributer. Neptune Ave. and West 21st St.
- Cahill, William, 1868
  House, sign and decorative painter and paper hanger. 234 Henry Street, bet'n Atlantic and Pacific
- Cain, John V., 1929
  Judge. 8070 Harbor View Terrace
- Calder, William M. Co., 1940
  Builders. 2703 Avenue U
- Caledonian Hospital, 1930
  Hospital. Corner St. Paul's and Woodruff Avenue
- Callahan, Patrick E., 1931
  Plumbing and heating. 311 54th Street
- Callahan, Wm J., 1879
  House, sign and ornamental painter. 331 Court Street
- Campbell, James, 1879, 1889
  Carpenter and builder. 232 State Street, near Court
- Campbell, John, 1872
  Crockery and glass dealer. 106 Fulton Street, opposite Prospect St.
- Camps, Manuel, 1909
  Cigar makers. 178 Ralph Avenue
- Canarsie Board of Trade, 1930
  9207 Flatlands Avenue
- Canavan, John, 1898
  Horseshoer. 57 Greenpoint Avenue
- Canda, M.M. Company, 1898
  Building materials dealer. Yard, 3rd St. and Gowanus Canal
- Carey, C.W., 1885
  Carpenter and builder. 175 Bayard Street
- Carhart, J., 1871
  Coal and wood dealer. Successor to A.W. Hendrickson. 82 Bridge Street, near York
- Carley, Edward, 1888
  Plumber, steam and gas fitter. 51 Greenpoint Avenue
- Carlisle, Wm. S., 1883
  Grocer and tea dealer. 493 Fulton Street
- Carll, J.P. & Co., 1870
  Carpet Dealer. Successors to Husted & Carll. 295 Fulton and 236 & 238 Washington Sts.
- Carll, John S., 1877
  Plumber, steam and gas fitter. 681 Atlantic Avenue
- Carney, John, 1872
  Coal dealer. 79 Washington Street
- Carr, Reuben P., 1867, 1874
  Mason and builder. 308 & 310 Bridge Street
- Carrick, H. & Son, 1882-1883
  Painters and paper hangers. Cor. Broadway and 11th Street
- Carroll, F., 1869
  Plumber, gas and steam fitter. 370 Myrtle Avenue bet. Cumberland St. and Carlton Ave.
- Carrougher, J.A., 1896, 1898
  Tin and sheet iron worker. 378 7th Avenue, bet. 11th and 12th Sts.
- Carruthers, F.W., 1877, 1879, 1882
  Real estate and insurance. 1357 Fulton Street
- Carruthers, J., 1897-1898
- Carruthers & Mills, 1897
  Carpenters and builders. 91 7th Avenue
- Carter, Alanson, 1881
  Furnaces, stoves, house furnishings etc.. 530 Fulton Street
- Cartwright, Charles J. & Co., 1930
  Real estate and insurance. 81 Fifth Avenue
- Cary & Stevenson, 1878
  Real estate and insurance. 196 Fulton Street
- Case & Powell, 1865
  Produce, flour, meal, feed, etc.. Flatbush Avenue opp. L.I. Railroad Depot and 14 Atlantic Street, South Ferry
- Cash, Thomas F., 1924
  Plumbing and gas fitting. Cor. Mermaid Ave. and West 30th St.
- Caspar & Sommerlad, 1895
  Anituqe furniture, wood polishing and varnishing. 30 Boerum Place
- Cassidy, F., 1871
  Lace curtain cleaning. 247 Jay Street
- Cassion, P., 1880
  Grocer. 463 Court Street, near Luqueer [Luquer?] St.
- Cathcart, George, 1883, 1886, 1887
  Mason and builder. 169 Classon Avenue, bet. Myrtle and Park; 513 Myrtle Avenue, near Grand; 560 Myrtle Ave
- Caton Laundry, 1920
  Laundry. 712 Flatbush Avenue
- Caulkins & Wilbur, 1889
  Carpet, oil cloths, shades etc. Successors to Geo. H. Titus. 613 & 615 Fulton Street
- Cavanagh(, Flaherty) & Cassidy, 1879, 1887-1889
  Gardeners. Calvary Cemetery, Long Island
- Cavanagh, James & Co., 1877, 1879, 1880
  Livery stable. 418 Court Street, bet. 1st & 2nd Place
- Cedar Rapids Baseball Club, 1955
  Affiliate of Brooklyn Dodgers Farm System.
- Celler & Co., 1891
  Liquor dealers. 31 Sumner, 857 and 859 Park Avenues
- Central Bank of Brooklyn, 1861
- Central Presbyterian Church, Trustees of, 1863-1864
- Central Sales Rooms, 1878
  Willoughby, corner of Pearl Street
- Chamber of Commerce of the Rockaways, 1931
  Chamber of Commerce Building, Far Rockaway, NY
- Chambers, James, 1867
  Shoe store. 280 Fulton Street
- Champagne, J., 1910
  Bicycles, motorcycles and sporting goods. 368 Sutter Avenue
- Chandler Brothers / Chickering Piano and Music Rooms, 1879
  Music rooms and sheet music. 172 Montague Street
- Chapman, W.E., 1870
  Dealer in masons' materials. Foot of South First Street
- Chappel, William, 1864-1865